Guide to the Amsterdam News photograph archive, Series B-MT, 1920-2012.
Amsterdam News photograph archive
- Series E. Dated Folders, 1990s
  - Jul. 10 & Aug. 14, 1993 (Box E-2, Folder 2)
    Photographer if identified: Julia Lemberger, Claude Gassian, E. Nat Roberts Jr., Richard Simpson, Bob Gruen, Morgenthaus for D.A., Tanzania Information Services, Karl Crutchfield, Dan/Jack/Steve Miller, Stella Magloire, Arnold Turner, Chris Cuffaro, Luiz Luppi, Handy's Photo Service, Austin Hansen, Stephen Danelian, Rodney K. Hurley, Kathryn Kirk, Willie Alleyne Associates, Bill Moore, Robert W. Cottrol
  - Jul. 17, 1993 (Box E-2, Folder 3)
    Also one leaf removed from an unidentified publication and 11 halftone prints. 10 prints have staples through the border.
    Photographer if identified: Kip Meyer, Peterkin Photo, Mel Wright, Karl Crutchfield
  - Jul. 24, 1993 (Box E-2, Folder 4)
    Also 19 halftone prints. 11 prints have staples through the border; 1 has a staple through the corner of the image.
    Photographer if identified: Robert Lewis, Nick White, Bill Moore, Karl Crutchfield, Stephanie Berger, Lem Peterkin, Ira Block, George Holz, Catherine Millet
  - Jul. 31 & Aug. 7, 1993 (Box E-2, Folder 5)
    Also 33 halftone prints, 2 images removed from an unidentified publications, and one photocopied graph.
    Photographer if identified: Ernest Harsch, NYC Dept. of Correction/Public Affairs, Nat Roberts Jr., Werner J. Kuhn, Beuford Smith, Kwame Brathwaite, Shirley Barenholz, Walt Disney Co., Ray Juschkus, Chuck Pulin, Dave Greene, Lois Greenfield, Anthony Barboza
  - Sept. 4, 1993 (Box E-2, Folder 6)
    Also one faxed image, one photocopied image, 4 halftone prints, and 3 images removed from unidentified publications. One print has a faxed leaf containing a graph stuck to the verso with tape. 9 prints have staples through the border.
    Photographer if identified: Karl Crutchfield, Fred W. Kelly, Jem Lew, Philip J. Carvalho, Pictorial Enterprise, Bill Moore, NYC Housing Authority
  - Sept. 11, 1993 (Box E-2, Folder 7)
    Also flier for OTB (with smaller photocopy), 2 leaves of graphs relating to OTB (with one leaf of ms. notes attached with staple), 4 images removed from unidentified publications, 2 photocopied images, and 17 halftone prints.
    Photographer if identified: Tony Akeem, Bill Moore, Nick Vaccaro, Fordham University/University Relations, NYC Housing Authority Photo Unit, NYC Dept. of Correction/Public Affairs, J. Abresch
  - Sept. 18, 1993 (Box E-2, Folder 8)
    One print is a Polaroid. 2 prints stuck together with tape. 7 prints have staples through border. Also 25 halftone prints, 1 leaf of ms. notes, one photocopied image, one computer-printed image, one page design form completed in ms., 2 images removed from unidentified publications, and Jun. 1993 issue of What's Up Downtown.
    Photographer if identified: Karl Crutchfield, Howie Evans, Lem Peterkin, Deborah Feingold, Andy Feldman, Bill Moore, Allen Morgan Photo, William Coupon, William Baker, Nancie Battaglia, Beth Green Studios
    Number of Prints: 58
  - Oct. 2, 1993 (Box E-2, Folder 9)
    Also 7 halftone prints and one image removed from an unidentified publication. One print is a Polaroid. 7 prints have staples through the border; one print has a staple through the corner of the image.
    Photographer if identified: Bill Moore, Frank Mohalley, John Maguire/Matar Studio, Rita E. Henderson, Kathryn Kirk
  - Oct. 23, 1993 (Box E-2, Folder 10)
    One print is a Polaroid. Also 11 halftone prints, 2 computer-printed images, and one photocopied image. 3 prints have staples through the border. 2 prints are stuck together with tape.
    Photographer if identified: Joe Pineiro, Karl Crutchfield, H. Frederick Stucker, Luigi, Janice Shindler Service, George West, TAR, Chris Callas
  - Oct. 30, 1993 (Box E-2, Folder 11)
    Also photocopy of election ballot (1 leaf), 4 halftone prints, and 2 images removed from unidentified publications. Three prints have staples through the border; one has a staple through the corner of the image.
    Photographer if identified: Marian Rich, Harris Photo, Lisa Schwair, Karl Crutchfield, Irving Kaufman Studios
  - Nov. 6, 1993 (Box E-2, Folder 12)
    3 prints have staples through border, 2 have staples through corner of image.
    Photographer if identified: Karl Crutchfield, Bill Moore, Melodie McDaniel, Peterkin Photo, Gill Photographers, Austin Hansen, Hakim Mutlaq, Allen Morgan, Karen Carrillo, Matthew Rolston, Dave Greene
  - Nov. 13, 1993 (Box E-2, Folder 13)
    One print is a Polaroid. Also 2 halftone prints. One print has staples through the border and the ms. caption from another print stuck with tape to the recto.
    Photographer if identified: Karl Crutchfield, Karen Zebulon, Bill Moore, Pavlos Petratos
  - Nov. 20, 1993 (Box E-2, Folder 14)
    Also original art and halftone copy of an editorial cartoon by Mel Tapley and one image removed from an unidentified publication. Two prints are attached together with tape at edges. 3 prints have staples through border.
    Photographer if identified: Metropolitan Photo Service, Karl Crutchfield, Bill Moore, Pamela Hamilton, Mel Peters, Leon T. Daniels Jr., Meredith, Roland L. Freeman, Gregory Mink, Jonathan Slaff, Hugh Brown, Marc Baruch
  - Nov. 20, 1993 (Box E-2, Folder 15)
    Faxed "Teen Express" header design, press release from United Help Outreach with ms. corrections (1 leaf with attached printer's instructions), faxed press release from the Allen African Methodist Episcopal Church with ms. corrections (1 leaf with attached printer's instructions), faxed press release from the New York KAGRO with ms. corrections (1 leaf with attached printer's instructions), faxed press release from the Mother A.M.E. Zion Church with ms. corrections (1 leaf with attached printer's instructions), computer-printed typescript text with ms. additions and corrections "'Lest We Forget,' Black musical..." by J. Zamga Brown (2 leaves), one leaf of ms. notes, approximately 35 leaves of newspaper page proofs (most with ms. corrections and additions), and approximately 70 leaves of newspaper page layout forms (some with original ms. notes, some photocopied).
  - Jan. 1, 1994 (Box E-2, Folder 16)
    One print has staple through border.
    Photographer if identified: George West, Bill Moore, Hakim Mutlaq, Karl Crutchfield, Susan F. Rymshaw, Lensman, Bud Smith Photography, Kathryn Kirk, Harlee Little, Marian Rich, United Press International Inc.
  - Jan. 1, 1994 (Box E-2, Folder 17)
    Also 7 prints removed from unidentified publications, one faxed image, 2 color plates removed from an unidentified publication, and one press release from Teen Magazine (1 leaf, with ms. corrections and annotations. Two prints have staples through the border. One print is mounted on a souvenir card from Kelly's Stable.
    Photographer if identified: Allen Morgan, Karl Crutchfield, James C. Campbell, Friedman-Abeles Photographers Inc.
  - Jan. 8, 1994 (Box E-2, Folder 18)
    One print is a photo-print business card. Also advertising postcard for the exhibit "Remembering the Duke" at Harlem Street Gallery International Inc., one halftone print, and two images removed from unidentified publications.
    Photographer if identified: Karl Crutchfield, Dave Greene, Bill Moore, Susan F. Rymshaw, Peterkin Photo, Harris Photo
  - Jan. 22, 1994 (Box E-2, Folder 19)
    Also one computer-printed image. 10 prints are pasted together on a single piece of paper. One print has a staple through the border.
    Photographer if identified: Edward Reed, Karl Crutchfield, Jim Belfon, William L. Ballinger, Jose Solano
  - Feb. 19, 1994 (Box E-2, Folder 20)
    Also two faxed images, one photocopied image, and one image removed from an unidentified magazine. One print has a staple through the border.
    Photographer if identified: Bert Andrews, Bud Smith, Carmen de Jesus, Hakim Mutlaq Fotos, Diane Bondareff, Karl Crutchfield, Will Cofnuk, Bruce Williams, Pictorial Enterprise
  - Feb. 26, 1994 (Box E-2, Folder 21)
    Also handbill for the Black Church National Day of Prayer for the Healing of AIDS (3-6-1994), 4 images removed from unidentified publications, and 2 faxed images. 2 prints have staples through the border, 2 prints have staples through the corner of the image.
    Photographer if identified: Karl Crutchfield, Bob Greene, James J. Kriegsmann, Philip J. Carvalho, Gregory Mink, Bodi Bakan, Lynda Downey
  - Mar. 12, 1994 (Box E-2, Folder 22)
    Also typescript editorial text "Marty Markowitz and the Convicted Rabbi" by Wilbert A. Tatum (2 leaves with attached newspaper clipping), computer-printed typescript letter signed by Marty Markowitz to Wilbert A. Tatum dated 3-1-1994 (2 leaves taped together as a single piece), photocopied letter from Robert Vasseur to "Editor" (1 leaf), 4 images removed from unidentified publications, one halftone print ,and 4 faxed images. One print has staple through border; one print has staple through corner of image.
    Photographer if identified: Karl Crutchfield, Juanita M. Cole, Preston Phillips, Otis Henderson
  - Mar. 26, 1994 (Box E-3, Folder 1)
    Also the Nov. 11, 1993 issue of the Ohio newspaper Call and Post, magazine article "Fannie Lou Hamer - 1917-1977" from the Apr. 25, 1977 issue of Seven Days (2 leaves), bottom portion only of a promotional leaflet from WABC-TV on Melba Tolliver, and one image removed from an unidentified publication. One print has staple through edge of image.
    Photographer if identified: NYU/Jon Roemer Photo, A. Hansen Studio, Karl Crutchfield, RJ Capak, Bill Moore, Maryanne Russell, Kathryn Kirk, Robert L. Haggins, Eric Liebowitz, Sigrid Estrada, Risasi-Zachariah Dais, Rapid News Service/Dummett, Gilbert Pictorial Enterprise
    Number of Prints: 61
  - Apr. 4, 1994 (Box E-3, Folder 2)
    Also 3 images removed from unidentified publications and one faxed image. One print is mounted on paperboard. 2 prints have staples through border.
    Photographer if identified: Eric Liebowitz, Ahmad, Ralph Cooper, Bill Moore, Karl Crutchfield, Jerry [L. Tuteel?], King Photographers, A. Hansen Studio, Lem Peterkin, James Gilbert/News Voice International, Pictorial Enterprise, Jet Commercial Photographers Inc., Visual Communications Ltd./Ahmad, Photos by Luigi
  - [no label] (Box E-3, Folder 3)
    Also one offset-printed promotional leaflet, 4 images removed from unidentified publications, and one halftone print. 2 prints have staples through the border.
    Photographer if identified: Will Cofnuk, Wade Nash, James Griesman, Norfolk State University Office of University Relations, Eric Prideaux, Joe Vericker/Photobureau Inc., Karl Crutchfield, Bill Moore, Gill Photographers, YMCA of Greater New York, United Press International Inc., James Gilbert, David M. Grossman Photography
  - Apr. 16, 1994 (Box E-3, Folder 4)
    Also one faxed image, original artwork (unsigned, [by Mel Tapley?]) for a spot illustration (1 leaf), screening invitation for the film Sugar Hill, advertising postcard for Henry House banquet hall, 2 images removed from unidentified publications, and one computer-printed image. Henry House postcard is stuck to the verso of a photo print.
    Photographer if identified: Pictorial Enterprise, Karl Crutchfield, Ahmad Ameri, Susan Tatum, Bill Moore, Rich Pipeling, Dina Alfano, TAR
  - Apr. 23, 1994 (Box E-3, Folder 5)
    Also one uncut sheet of 3 handbills from the American Liver Foundation, one offset-printed headshot, one promotional mailing pamphlet for Max Roach (postmarked 10-4-1971), 3 images removed from unidentified publications, one photocopied image, one faxed image, and one halftone print. One print has staple through corner of image, 2 prints have staples through border.
    Photographer if identified: N.Y. Daily News, Bill Moore, Karl Crutchfield, Kate Garner, James Gilbert, Bert Andrews, Marc Baruch, George Frye, Harrod Blank, Martha Cooper, Brown Brothers, American Lamb Council, Dave Greene Photo, Gerhard Jurkovic, Allen Morgan, Pictorial Enterprise
  - Apr. 30, 1994 (Box E-3, Folder 6)
    Also photocopy of page dummy from another newspaper (the Sowetan), 3 images removed from unidentified publications, and one halftone print. 3 prints have staples through border, one has staple through corner of image.
    Photographer if identified: John Vecchiolla, Karl Crutchfield, Domenic Difiglia, NYC Housing Authority Photo Unit, Standard Studios, Bill Moore, John J. Cruz, Peterkin Photo, L. Racioppo, Harris Photo, James Gilbert
  - May 7, 1994 (Box E-3, Folder 7)
    2 prints have staples through border; one print has staple through corner of image. Also partial brochure from WNYC-TV and 2 faxed images.
    Photographer if identified: Rich Lubell, Dina Alfano, Karl Crutchfield, Marvin T. Jones & Associates, United Press International Photo, Gill Photographers, Allen Morgan, Norman Frederick, Sherlock Robinson, Carol Lockett/Garza, Bill Moore, Sickle Cell Center
  - May 14, 1994 (Box E-3, Folder 8)
    Also anti-police brutality flier, photocopied press release dated 5-9-1994 concerning the death of Ernest Sayon, advertising card for Sheila's Restaurant and Jazz Room (in 2 sections), photocopy (with one ms. addition pasted on) of artwork for a cartoon by Chris Acemandese Hall ("Little Zeng Speaks"), 7 halftone prints, 2 computer-printed images, and one leaf of faxed images. Two groups of small prints are mounted on paper (one set of 3 prints, one set of 4 prints).
    Photographer if identified: Carol Rosegg/Martha Swope Associates, Juanita M. Cole, Saunders Associates, Karl Crutchfield, John Vecchiolla, Lloyd Terry, George Holz, Allen Morgan Photo, Sandra Wavrick, Jonathan Smith, Kathryn Kirk, David Karp, Anita & Steve Shevett, Gerald Peart
    Number of Prints: 89
  - May 19, 1994 (Box E-3, Folder 9)
    Also one image removed from an unidentified publication, 3 photocopied images, and 4 halftone prints. 2 of the halftone prints are stuck together face-to-face. One print is a Polaroid.
    Photographer if identified: New York Power Authority, Karl Crutchfield, James Gilbert, Lynda Downey, William Ramos/City of Newark, Simon Benepe, Mel Wright
  - May 28, 1994 (Box E-3, Folder 10)
    One print is a Polaroid. 4 prints have staples through the border; 5 prints have staples through the corner of the image. Also 3 halftone prints, 3 computer-printed images, and 2 images removed from an unidentified publication.
    Photographer if identified: Karl Crutchfield, David Trancoso, Bruce W. Talamon, Pictorial Enterprise, Harris Photo, Kevin Ryan, Dan/Jack/Steve Miller, James Gilbert, Gregory Mink
  - Jun. 4, 1994 (Box E-3, Folder 11)
    Also 4 halftone prints, 2 faxed images (one with ms. additions), 2 color photocopied images, 2 images removed from unidentified publications, and one b&w photocopied image. 3 prints have staples through the corner of the image.
    Photographer if identified: Karl Crutchfield, Carvá, United Church of Christ Office of Communication, Harris Photo, James Gilbert, Philip J. Carvalho, Allen Morgan
  - Jun. 11, 1994 (Box E-3, Folder 12)
    Also one halftone print, one color photocopied image, and one b&w photocopied image. One print has staple through the corner of the image.
    Photographer if identified: William Ramos/City of Newark, Karl Crutchfield, Zelda Kaplin, Pictorial Enterprise, Bill Moore, John T. Hill, Keith Jenkins, Geoffrey Miller, Boston University Photo Services
  - Jun. 25, 1994 (Box E-3, Folder 13)
    Also p. 1-2 and 55-56 only (front and back cover) of the Jun. 20, 1994 issue of the Daily News and one photocopied image. One print has a staple through the border; one print has a staple through the corner of the image.
    Photographer if identified: Paige Stevens, Karl Crutchfield, Ronald L. Glassman, Gerald Peart, Lisa Schwair, Tom Brazil, James Gilbert
  - Jul. 9, 1994 (Box E-3, Folder 14)
    Also one offset-printed headshot, one sample check for David B. and Katherine L. Sheffield, and one faxed image. One print has a staple through the border.
    Photographer if identified: Rocco Galatloto/CMC, Gerald Peart, Lem Peterkin, James Barnett, Michael Tighe, Phil Caruso, Tom Matthews Photography
  - Jul. 30, 1994 (Box E-3, Folder 15)
    Also hand-drawn Prince symbol (1 leaf), press screening pamphlet for the movie The Client, 5 images removed from unidentified publications, 2 halftone prints, one computer-printed image, one photocopied image, and one faxed image. Two prints have staples through the corner of the image; one print has a staple through the border.
    Photographer if identified: Karl Crutchfield, Rodney K. Hurley, Louis Boone, Bill Moore, Lisa Schwair, Steve Friedman, Austin Hansen, Chuck Stewart
  - Jul. 30, 1994 (Box E-3, Folder 16)
    Also one offset-printed handbill of headshots for Billy Graham and one halftone print. 2 prints have staples through the border.
    Photographer if identified: Karl Crutchfield, Bill Moore, Port Authority of NY/NJ, Austin Hansen, Howie Evans, Bronx Community College, Ali Rahman, Anthony Barboza, Jill Posener, George West, Peggy Jarrell Kaplan
  - Oct. 6, 1994 (Box E-3, Folder 17)
    Also brochure "Dee Evelyn Matthews for National President" published by Continental SocietiesInc. (dated Jun. 1956), funeral card for Carmen D. Hicks, 2 leaves of photocopied clothing designs sketches, one computer-printed image, one photo caption printed on photo paper, 7 images removed from unidentified publications, one faxed image, and 2 halftone prints. One halftone print is stuck to a menu from Zen Palate. One print is an NYPD Missing Persons report (printed with a color image on photo paper). 2 prints have staples through border.
    Photographer if identified: Karl Crutchfield, Dawoud Bey, Dwight Carter, Dan/Jack/Steve Miller, Dwight Carter, Joe Lopez, Samir Id-Deen, Sam Emerson, Peterkin Photo, Joe Vericker/Photobureau Inc., Diane Bondareff, Davogre Photo Studio, Malcolm Pinckney
  - Mar. 5, 1995 (Box E-3, Folder 18)
    Also printed headshot and biography of Ousmane Gueye, one image removed from an unidentified publication, one faxed image, and one computer-printed image. One print has a staple through the border.
    Photographer if identified: Carol Friedman, Andreas Johnsen, Al Burley, Bill Moore, Karl Crutchfield, Bill Hawthorne, James Gilbert, Winnie Klotz, Dona Ann McAdams, Pictorial Enterprise
  - [no label] (Box E-3, Folder 19)
    Also one halftone print. 2 prints have staples through border.
    Photographer if identified: Rodney K. Hurley, Bill Moore, Jerry Bauer, NBC, Wendy Bradley, Pictorial Enterprise, Peterkin Photo
  - [no label] (Box E-3, Folder 20)
    Also original art for a cartoon by Mac McGill ("Tyson Toons") and 73 velox prints. 2 prints have staples through the border.
    Photographer if identified: Bill Moore, Goddy WichenDu C., Joan Vitale Strong, Curt Clemons, Larry Brown, Pictorial Enterprise
  - [no label] (Box E-3, Folder 21)
    Also press release dated 6-4-1991 from the Cooper-Hewitt Museum (1 leaf) and 38 velox prints.
    Photographer if identified: Richard Watkins, Curt Clemons, Bill Moore
  - [no label] (Box E-3, Folder 22)
    Also original artwork for an editorial cartoon by Martin McGill ("Here I come to save the day!"), offset-printed leaf of illustrations entitled "Hair Routes," 4 halftone prints, and one illustration removed from an unidentified publication. 3 prints have staples through border.
    Photographer if identified: Anita & Steve Shevett, Peterkin Photo, Hakim Mutlaq Fotos, Kwame Brathwaite, Gregory Mink, Veronica Saddler, Allen Morgan Photo, Jonathan Slaff, Paul Knowles, Bill Moore, Kathryn Kirk, Karl Crutchfield, Pictorial Enterprise, Barry Love, Livingstone College Public Relations Office, Bert Andrews
  - [no label] (Box E-3, Folder 23)
    Also cover only from the program for the New York Philharmonic's 14th Annual Free Outdoor Concert, offset-printed headshot of Linda Arlett, 4 halftone prints, photocopy of a sketch of O.J. Simpson by Mel Tapley (1 leaf), 5 images removed from unidentified publications, and one photocopied newspaper clipping. 2 prints have staples through corner of image.
    Photographer if identified: Melissa Springer, Lem Peterkin, Dagmar Schultz, Howie Evans, Bill Moore, Karl Crutchfield, Public Education Assocation, Allen Morgan, Judith Liegner Artists' Management
  - [no label] (Box E-3, Folder 24)
    Also faxed article text "Ousted NAACP Leader to Tell All" (1 leaf, with ms. corrections), one faxed image, and 3 halftone prints. 2 prints have staples through the border.
    Photographer if identified: Joan Vitale Strong, Karl Crutchfield, Joe Pineiro, Allen Morgan, Gill Photographers, Joan Tedeschi, James Gilbert, Austin Hansen
  - [no label] (Box E-3, Folder 25)
    Photographer if identified: Hakim Mutlaq, HE Photo, Karl Crutchfield, Bill Moore, Popsie, Kathryn Kirk, David M. Grossman
  - [no label] (Box E-3, Folder 26)
    Also original artwork for an editorial cartoon by Mac McGill ("It's sooooooo simple!") and one velox print. 3 prints have staples through border, 2 have staples through corner of image.
    Photographer if identified: Al Jordan, Karl Crutchfield, William B. Carter, Peter H. Bick, Keith Williams/Louisville Journal-Courier, Allen Morgan, Peterkin Photo, Granville Allen/Jamaica Tourist Board, Bill Moore, Kwame Brathwaite, Joseph Maynard, Rooz Paolo, Elena Borstein, Joan Vitale Strong, Billy Pierce Jr.
  - [no label] (Box E-3, Folder 27)
    Also one photocopied image. One print is an NYPD Missing Persons report (printed with a color image on photo paper). 8 prints have staples through the border.
    Photographer if identified: Vilma Farrar, William L. Ballinger, Joan Vitale Strong, George West, Peterkin Photo, R.J. Clark, Bill Moore, Karl Crutchfield, Miles Educational Film Prods Inc., Dan Luhmann, Luigi, Gregory Mink, Harlem Photographic Society
- Series F. Sports Photos
  Mostly promotional photos from sports teams.
  - Atlanta Braves (Box F-1, Folder 1)
  - Atlanta Hawks (Box F-1, Folder 2)
  - Baltimore Colts (Box F-1, Folder 3)
  - Baltimore Orioles (Box F-1, Folder 4)
  - Boston Celtics (Box F-1, Folder 5)
  - Boston Patriots (Box F-1, Folder 6)
  - Boston Red Sox (Box F-1, Folder 7)
    Also a 1965 media guide.
  - Buffalo Braves (Box F-1, Folder 8)
  - Chicago Bears (Box F-1, Folder 9)
  - Chicago Bulls (Box F-1, Folder 10)
  - Chicago Cubs (Box F-1, Folder 11)
  - Chicago White Sox (Box F-1, Folder 12)
  - Cincinnati Reds (Box F-1, Folder 13)
  - Cleveland Browns (Box F-1, Folder 14)
    Photographer if identified: Gilbert Pictorial
  - Cleveland Cavaliers (Box F-1, Folder 15)
  - Cleveland Indians (Box F-1, Folder 16)
  - Colgate University (Football) (Box F-1, Folder 17)
  - Dallas Cowboys (Box F-1, Folder 18)
  - Denver Broncos (Box F-1, Folder 19)
  - Denver Nuggets (Box F-1, Folder 20)
  - Detroit Lions (Box F-1, Folder 21)
  - Detroit Pistons (Box F-1, Folder 22)
  - Detroit Tigers (Box F-1, Folder 23)
  - Gauchos (Box F-1, Folder 24)
    Photographer if identified: Marty Cobin
  - Golden State Warriors (Box F-1, Folder 25)
  - Green Bay Packers (Box F-1, Folder 26)
    Photographer if identified: Laughead Photographers
  - Harlem Globetrotters (Box F-1, Folder 27)
  - Houston Astros (Box F-1, Folder 28)
  - Houston Rockets (Box F-1, Folder 29)
  - Indiana Pacers (Box F-1, Folder 30)
  - Kansas City Chiefs (Box F-1, Folder 31)
  - Kansas City Kings (Box F-1, Folder 32)
  - Los Angeles Angels (Box F-1, Folder 33)
  - Los Angeles Dodgers (Box F-1, Folder 34)
  - Los Angeles Lakers (Box F-1, Folder 35)
  - Los Angeles Rams (Box F-1, Folder 36)
    Photographer if identified: Vic Stein
  - Little League, Mets (Box F-1, Folder 37)
  - Milwaukee Bucks (Box F-1, Folder 38)
  - Minnesota Twins (Box F-1, Folder 39)
  - Minnesota Vikings (Box F-1, Folder 40)
    Photographer if identified: Sports Productions Inc.
  - New Jersey Nets (Box F-1, Folder 41)